A Guide to the Anderson-Latham Collection, 1777-1881
Library of Virginia
- Joseph Kerr Papers, 1788-1836 (Box 10)
  - Cancelled Checks, 1812, 1815 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Chilicothe Farm Slaughter Ledger, 1811-1812 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1788-1824 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Deed of Conveyance, 1836 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Letters of Administration, Estate of James Daugherty, 1798 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Lists of Land Warrants (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Powers of Attorney (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Promissory Note, 1812 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Receipts (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Sales of Cargo, 1812-1814 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Suit Papers (Box 10, Folder 16-25)
  - Survey, 1806 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Tax Receipts, 1800-1814 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Oversized Items (Box 11)
  The oversized items include accounts, assignments, circulars, deeds, a letter from Timothy Pickering to Governor Robert Brooke, plats and surveys, powers of attorney, and tax receipts.
  - Accounts (Joseph Kerr), 1812-1813 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - An Act to Quiet Land Titles in the Virginia Military District Northwest of the Ohio River, 1842 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Assignments (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Bill of Fare, 1853 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Claims for Property Lost or Destroyed While in Military Service (circular), 1817 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Columbus and Xenia Railroad Company Bond and Coupons, 1850 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Compensation of Benjamin Hough and Alexander Holmes as Deputy Surveyors, 1817 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Deeds, 1806-1822 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Letter, Timothy Pickering to Gov. Robert Brooke, 13 June 1795 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Lists of Individuals Entitled to Bounty Land (circulars), 1821-1822 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Plats and Surveys (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Powers of Attorney, 1798-1823 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Tax Receipts, 1813, 1818 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Plat and List of Lots Located Agreeable to Lottery on 5 July 1819